I've also eaten, um...
Vegan sausage rolls.
Have you eaten a vegan sausage roll?
I've not, but it's meant to be a monster hit for that bakery chain, isn't it?
I don't know why people...
Why are you laughing for?
Chris, why are you laughing for?
I'm being serious!
No, you see...
No, you see, I'm talking facts here.
I don't do if, buts and maybes.
I do absolutes.
And, you know, like, if your aunt had balls, she'd be your uncle.
But she doesn't, so she's not.
Do you know what I'm trying to say?
Who?  Exactly.
Who?  He knows.
My man knows.
Do you know what I mean?
Listen.
Does Brexit make my passport expire?
No.
But it does mean that you are entitled to a beautiful new blue passport.
Tomorrow.
It's tomorrow.
No, it's tomorrow.
Butter.
Listen.
That's it.
Say it again.
Butter.
In the run-up to any competition, Danny's trainer puts him on a strict diet.
Eight o'clock in the morning, I'll have fish and a rice cake.
At ten o'clock, I'll have fish.
At twelve o'clock, I'll have fish and a rice cake.
At two o'clock, I'll have fish.
At four o'clock, just before a train, I'll have fish and a rice cake.
I'll train.
I'll have me fish.
I'll come home, have some more fish.
So this is my lovely, lovely dress.
Loved my dress.
White was obviously a bit dodgy.
Can you see the yellow stains and all sorts of stuff?
Now, before you jump to any conclusions where these mysterious yellow stains might have come from,
I can tell you that those are in fact mustard and pick a lily.
Woah, woah, woah.
Mysterious girl.
Move your body close to mine.
Come on, move your body.
I stop and stare at you.
Walking on the shore.
I try to concentrate.
My mind wants to explore.
To explore.  The tropical scene of you takes me up above.
And girl, when I look at you, oh, I fall in love.
No doubt you look so fine.
Woah.
Girl, I want to make you mine.
Yeah, come on.
Just let me be with the woman that I love.
The woman that I love.
Where's the lamb sauce?
Come on, man.
I just need it.
There's the lamb sauce.
Where's the lamb sauce?
Do you think these **** are going to pay my mortgage?
I've got money.
Listen, Gemma.
I'm claustrophobic, Darren.
Listen.
They don't get it.
I'm claustrophobic.
The voting lines have officially closed.
The votes have been counted and verified.
Could you please have quiet in the studio?
Quite please.
**** shut up!
Thank you.
Message?
Oh, from Michelle.
How very amusing.
Say, would you like to watch it together?
Yes.
Let's have a look.
Hey, Prince Harry.
Remember when you told us to bring it at the Invictus Games?
Careful what you wish for.
Boom.
Oh, really?
Please.
Boom.
My name is Jonathan Pye and that was the **** news.
Mr. Broccoli, you went viral on the internet
because you were arrested and you were a piece of broccoli.
Yes.
Do you identify as broccoli?
I am Mr. Broccoli, yes.
Yes, that's right, please.
Do you have another name or not?
No, Mr. Broccoli is...
That's it.
You don't go about your daily business as a piece of broccoli.
I've always been a piece of broccoli.
Really?  Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Right.
So do you have a job?
I just grow.
Do you know who I am?
Do I care?
Well, you will when you pull up.
Come on, who are you then?
Ronan Bickering.
Who?  Ronan Bickering.
Who the **** is that?
Yeah, me.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Brilliant.
That's literally the first thing I do.
There's always one.
I'm going to chop the end of my finger off.
Might have to sit outside for a bit.
A bit like...
Keep walking.
Slowly.
Oh, dear.